hello this is ton the owner and founder
of the y sky ph
all about vol
[Music]
product
i am a proud financial advisor who can
help you and your journey toward
financial freedom however this video
only reflects my personal views and
opinions
about
money to your family in case you are
called too soon
so basically you don't buy life
insurance because someone has to die you
buy life insurance because
someone has to continue
it serves as a repayment or an act of
gratitude
[Music]
investment so insurance at investment i
view a plan
i send you a plan and an offering is
that can be paid for a minimum of 10
years combining the benefits and
insurance and investments in some plan
so under market futures
minimum of 10 years to pay but i've been
having minimum of 10 years
10 years
at least 10 years second insurance with
investment plans and third
and then later don't i use an investment
part insurance and live insurance
coverage
until age 88 that i'm paying period i at
least 10 years a minimum face amount
350.
known as two times num face amount
at 350 000 and live insurance
times two or seven hundred thousand
pesos
guaranteed
[Music]
the accumulation period so after 10
years generate a ligament experience
young growth non-investment more
next question is investment guaranteed
the answer is
[Music]
for the next 10 years
on medical benefits
hiv until age 16 of the age at an abd at
sea
until age 17 and your life insurance
coverage
until age 88.
[Music]
say santa one day and 4 615
add new hiv 5 foreign critical illness 5
8. so for a total of 67 490.
s
so for
[Music]
every year
pesos
go so your index fund is ten percent and
marami bank investment finance
for the sake of example
in reality
investment fund depending on your risk
appetite
and investors
however through time after 40 years so
in 65 bahunan 10 million nasa bureau in
million 656 000 go after 10 years
10.97 million
guaranteed it can be more it can be less
nothing so until such time you saw 10
years almost equal
humiliation
investment growth
second part investment
advantages at disadvantages now 10 years
to pay in the video
advantage
2 in one life insurance plan my
insurance card
investment in one second your investment
fund or your investment more
professionally management experience
chen five years 10 years 15 years 20
years or more
investment third advantage and flexible
payment schemes
and
[Music]
computation
management
my money after 10 years and my insurance
is still in effect
investment
in the future
next question how will my money be
divided in this plan how much will go to
my investment so an explanation
first three years more on insurance than
investments
keep in mind insurance plan
[Music]
foreign
next question can a person with ckd
diabetes hiv and other health concerns
can get this plan the answer
please click the like share and
subscribe button
about personality
[Music]
you